(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T12:52:49.446325",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Good day, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to the Queen Mother theater.
May I remind you to unwrap the snacks you may wish to nom,
and please switch your mobile phones on, as photography is allowed!
Please feel free to take screenshots during the performance using the hashtag #ERB3D.
Spread your Queen's performance far and wide.
本日は「Queen Motherシアター」へご来場いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for visiting the Queen Mother Theater today.
開演に先立ち、いくつかご案内申し上げます。
Before the curtain rises, we have a few announcements.
館内での飲食は大歓迎です。お持ちのお菓子はどうぞご自由にお楽しみください。
Food and drink are very welcome inside. Please enjoy your snacks freely.
本公演は撮影OK！携帯電話は電源オンのままで、スクリーンショットには
Photography is allowed! Keep your mobile phones powered on,
ERB3Dのハッシュタグを添え、ぜひSNSにご投稿して、女王陛下の魅力を世界の隅々までお届けしてください。
and please post screenshots on social media with the hashtag #ERB3D to share Her Majesty's charm across the world.
Thank you, and enjoy the performance!
Hazzah!
さあ、それでは間もなく開演の時間です。どうぞお席にて、
Now then, it is almost time for the curtain to rise.
女王陛下の舞台を心ゆくまでお楽しみください。
Please take your seats and enjoy Her Majesty's stage to your heart's content.
はっざー！
Hazzah!
Hey ya! Hey ya!
Get the hell out of my way! What the frig?
I don't have time to deal with the likes of you! Back off and stay back!
Darling.
Know your place! I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
...blood flame... and those who dare interfere with me shall receive no mercy.
...bloodflame! And those who dare interfere with me shall receive no mercy.
Good grief... And today of all days, my commemorative 3D showcase
getting ambushed like this has been quite troublesome.
Starts with all the showcase preparations and practice I need to do.
Starting with all the showcase preparations and practice I need to do,
I can't afford to waste time on something like this.
There's not enough hours in the day! How annoying!
All right, you pop yourself there, Thornstay there, stay there.
Listen to this. My self-introduction...
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order,
leader of justice, I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you, lovely!
How was that?
Tough crowd. Oh gosh, I'm so behind. We need to get to the karaoke by stone, come on, let's go!
Tough crowd. Oh gosh, I'm so behind. We need to get to the karaoke by sunset, come on, let's go!
What the frig?
You lot again? You never learn, do you?
All right, I guess it's time for round two.
Oh my god, down!
You dare wound my flames? You'll pay for this!
Very well. I'll deal with you...
...while practicing a song for my 3D showcase.
Two birds, one stone. Listen well.
Hazzah!
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted,
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show.
泣いていても笑っていても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me, okay?
ほら Say No 低音響かせろ
Come on, say no, now let's bring the bass.
なんだかなって つまんないこともあるでしょう
Don't know what to say, things tend to get boring,
ロンリー論理のノート ハンディー本気脱走
Lonely logic note, handy serious escape.
やんなっちちゃって泥に Bad
Can't take this anymore, it's bad taboo,
ご法度だろが 浸れて墜ちて
But drown and drop in mud, it's about time.
そろそろいっか もっと頑張って
Let's work harder, let's work harder
アガるまでもっと頑張って
until I get excited.
繋がろうひとりよりふたり
Let's connect, two is better than one,
増えたら安心 心配ないや
More the people, more I'm relieved.
Alright 任せて don't mind
Alright, let me do it, don't mind.
波あり難題 みんなで乗っかっちゃえば
If we all ride the waves of problems,
案外さくっ と行ってしまいそう
perhaps it's easy to solve.
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted,
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show.
泣いていても笑っていても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me, okay?
ほら Say No 低音響かせろ
Come on, say no, now let's bring the bass.
今宵は暗転パーティー
Yeah, tonight's a party in the dark,
Woah
Woah-oh-oh.
踊りだせ 踊りだせ
Dance, dance,
孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Sanitize loneliness, it's full house.
Woah
Woah-oh-oh.
痛みまで おシェアで
Even the pain, let's share it,
ここらでバイバイ let go
It's time to say bye-bye, let go.
どんな劣等感だてて
Any complex, with a free-style platelet,
即興の血小板で
Hold it, shove it, take it away.
抑え込んで 突っ込んで
Pumped up and down, pretty much stressed out,
仕舞い込んじゃうでしょ
Spit it out at once, and give yourself away.
Up and down なテンション
Not really interested,
ねぇまえいっちきちゅうねの相応
Don't really care,
ドバっと噴き出すのは
Forget these feelings, I'ma say what I want.
本音の独り言
Send signal.
「別に興味ない」 「特に関係ない」
Let's come together, live the night,
塞ぎ込んで 舌鋒絶頂へ
We be roaring.
合図を奏でて PrrPrrPrr
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ほら集まって夜行だ
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
鳴いているいこう
Ooh-woah-oh-ooh-oh.
半端なら K.O.
Dance, dance.
Woah
Sanitize loneliness, it's full house.
踊りだせ 踊りだせ
Even the pain, let's share it.
孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Tonight's a party in the dark.
Woah
We look forward to serving you again.
痛みまで おシェアで
Please take care until next time,
今宵も暗転パーティーだ
It's time to say bye-bye, let go.
またのお越しを きっと
We look forward to serving you again.
Woah
Ooh-woah-oh-ooh-oh.
次回までお元気で
Please take care until next time.
ここらでバイバイ let go
It's time to say bye-bye, let go.
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me okay?
ほら say no 低音響かせろ
Come on, "Say No", now let's bring the bass
なんだかなって つまらないこともあるでしょう
Don't know what to say, things tend to get boring
ロンリー論理のノート ハンディ本気脱走
Lonely logic note, handy serious escape
やんなっちまって泥に bad
Can't take this anymore, it's bad taboo
ご法度だろうが 溺れて墜ちて そろそろいっか
But drown and drop in mud, it's about time
もっと頑張って アガるまでもっと頑張って
Let's work harder, let's work harder until I get excited
繋がろうひとりよりふたり
Let's connect, two is better than one
増えたら安心 心配ないや
More the people, more I'm relieved
Alright 任せて don't mind
Alright let me do it, don't mind
波あり難題 みんなで乗りかかっちゃえば 案外さくっと行っちゃいそうさ
If we all ride the waves of problems, perhaps it's easy to solve
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me okay?
ほら say no 低音響かせろ
Come on, "Say No", now let's bring the bass
今宵は暗転パーティ
Yeah, tonight's a party in the dark
Woah 踊らせだ 踊らせだ
Ooh-woah-oh-ooh-oh
孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Dance, dance
Woah 痛みまで おシェアで
Sanitize loneliness, it's full house, thank you
ここらでバイバイ let go
Ooh-woah-oh-ooh-oh
どんな劣等感だてて
即興の血小板で
Even the pain, let's share it
抑え込んで 突っ込んで 仕舞い込んじゃうでしょ
It's time to say bye-bye, let go
Up and down なテンション
Any complex, with a free-style platelet
ねえまえいっかっていんの相称
Hold it, shove it, take it away, aye
ドバッと噴き出すのは 本音の独り言
Pumped up and down, pretty much stressed out
「別に興味ない」
Spit it out at once, and give yourself away
「特に関係ない」
"Not really interested"
塞ぎ込んで 舌鋒絶頂へ
"Don't really care"
合図を奏でて PrrPrrPrr
Forget these feelings, i'ma say what I want
ほら集まって夜行だ 鳴いていこうぜ
Send signal (prr, prr, prr, prr, yeah)
半端なら K.O.
Let's come together, live the night
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah (ow!)
We be roaring
Woah 踊らせだ 踊らせだ
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah (ow!)
Woah 痛みまで おシェアで
Ooh-woah-oh-ooh-oh
今宵も暗転パーティだ
Woah またのお越しを きっと
Dance, dance
Woah 次回までお元気に
Sanitize loneliness, it's full house, thank you
Heaven, please sing for me a song of life
Heaven, take me into your skies
There's no place here for me to hide my cries
Night and day, i'm missing you
I know i'm here for the magic
All your stars guiding me through and through
(oh) why, this loneliness feel like... forever and ever
I gotta be, i gotta be, in your arms, baby
You're so close, so close
And it's you that i believe in, i believe in
So close, but far away so far i can't touch
I'll hold on.
'cuz it's you i love so dearly
When the rain, the storm, and all is done
Caress me with your sweet lullaby...
Heaven, please sing for me a song of life
Heaven, take me into your skies
There's no place here for me to hide my cries
Night and day, I'm missing you
Night and day, I call for you
Flashes of moments so tragic
Wondering souls, they fall along the way
Tell me you will never leave me forever and ever
I gotta be, I gotta be in your arms, hear me
You're so close, so close
So close, but faraway, so far I can't touch
And it's you that I believe in, I believe in
I'll hold on
'Cause it's you I love so dearly when the rain, the storm, and all is done
Caress me with your sweet lullaby
Will you be my light?
Will you be my strength?
Promise you won't let me go
I'll never betray
In the end of time
Still my love's gonna be there
You're so close, so close
And it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but faraway, so far I can't touch
I'll hold on
'Cause it's you I love so dearly when the rain, the storm, and all is done caress me with your sweet lullaby
You're so close, so close
And it's you that I believe in, I believe in
So close, but faraway, I seek for your light
I'll hold on
'Cause for you my heart keeps beating when the wind, the fire, and all is gone caress me with your sweet lullaby
This song is lovely, but for my showcase performance, should I pick nostalgic songs?
Oh, it's a call!
Ollie, my favorite zombie!
How are you, baby?
Hololive senpai, perfect timing. Actually, I'm having trouble deciding what to sing with my 3D showcase.
Yeah.
Is that so?
Well, I think I speak for everyone when I say, we'll be happy to hear you sing anything! As long as you're enjoying yourself, that is.
But isn't it standard to pick songs that match your image?
Mm, I see.
Well, you know how powerful you look when you sing? Yes, yes. So I thought, you know...
Why not try a cute song instead? Go for that Gap Moe appeal, you know what I'm saying?
A cute song, that would be different from usual, which would be good, but I'm a bit worried about doing it alone.
That's it! What if we invited my brothers-in-arms, arm-is as guests?
That's a great idea! Think, cool people singing cute songs? Oh, the Gap Moe will definitely get everybody excited!
Yeah, but it's still a tad embarrassing.
It'll be fine! Come on, try imagining it. Picture you and Armis singing a cute song together.
Me and Armis... cute song... to-together...
[Music]
私があたしの事を愛して
I love myself
何が悪いのか？ 嫉妬でしょうか？
What's wrong with that? Are you jealous?
痛いとか変わってるとか
They say I'm cringey or eccentric,
届きませんね。そのリプライ
but I won't listen to those comments!
大好きな「お洋服」
With my favorite clothes
大好きな「お化粧」で
and favorite makeup on,
お決まりの「ハーフツイン」巻いて お出かけしよう
I've got my iconic half-twintails curled. Let's go out!
日傘持って
Carrying a parasol,
ぼっちだって
all alone,
幸せだもん！
I'm happy!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
生まれ育ってごめん
Sorry that I was born.
Chu! あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being calculatingly cute.
気になっちゃうよね？ごめん
You can't ignore me, can you?
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for working hard on myself.
Chu! 尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious.
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for being a girly girl.
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまぁw
It annoys you, right? Serves you right! w
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
Chu! あざとくてごめん
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
Chu! あざとくてごめん
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
Chu! とおってもごめん
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまぁw
It annoys you, right? Serves you right! w
貴方は貴事だけどうぞ
You do your own thing,
私に干渉しないでください
so please don't meddle in my business.
類は友を呼ぶと言うけれど…
They say birds of a feather flock together...
届きませんね。その陰口
But I can't hear those behind-the-back gossips!
重い厚底ブーツ
With my heavy platform boots,
お気に入りのリュックで
favorite backpack,
崩せない前髪
and bangs that won't get ruined,
くせどいてお出かけしよう
let's go out!
軽い女？ふざけんな
An easygoing girl? Are you kidding me?
重すぎるっつーの！
That's way too much!
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
この時代生きててごめん
Sorry for living in this era.
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
Chu! この時代生きててごめん
Chu! 目立っててごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! 自分磨きしててごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
Chu! ぶりっこでごめん
Chu! 虜にしちゃってごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
ムカついちゃうでしょ？ざまぁw
It annoys you, right? Serves you right! w
趣味の違い 変われ者と
Even if people with different tastes
バカにされても
make fun of me as a weirdo,
曲げたくない 怖くもない
I won't change, and I'm not scared of you!
あんたらごと
You people and your moments...
自分の味方は自分でありたい
My greatest ally is myself.
一番大切にしてあげたい
I want to cherish myself the most.
理不尽な我慢はさせたくない
I don't want to accept unreasonable selfishness.
“それが私”
"This is me!"
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
生まれきてちゃってごめん
Sorry that I was born.
Chu! あざとくてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
人生楽しんでごめん
Sorry for enjoying my life.
Chu! 可愛くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
努力しちゃっててごめん
Sorry for working hard on myself.
Chu! 尊くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being precious.
女子力高くてごめん
Sorry for being a girly girl.
Chu! とってもごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
Chu! おどけてごめん
Chu! 女子力高くてごめん
Chu! Sorry for being so cute.
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまぁw
It annoys you, right? Serves you right! w
待って待って待って待って待って待って待って
Wait, wait, wait! Wait a minute!
待って待って待って私、私！私！私！私！私！私！
I'm not cut out to be a cute...
私！私！私！私！私！私！私！私！私！私！私！私！私！私！私！私！
cute, cute, cute, cute, cute lookin', man!
フフフフッ…
Haha...
That's not true!
I'm sure everyone wants to see that side of you, too, Liz!
So thank you, Ollie. I feel better about it since you think so.
Ollie's senpai makes me happy you think I'm cute, I'm a powerful...
Yeah, yeah! Powerful indeed!
Oh gosh, seems like it's the end of my karaoke room booking.
Rehearsal time is up here.
Ollie senpai, thank you so much!
All right, do your best, please!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
All shall— Okay, here we go!
Okay, let's go, let's go!
Oh, come on!
All right, here we go!
Whoa!
Hmm, my singing is fine,
but now the physical performance side of bits and bobs is what worries me.
I'm really not too confident...
about my dancing as I'm a... a tad rusty.
About my dancing, since I'm... a tad rusty.
Oh, what's wrong, Liz?
Zaa senpai! Wow, actually,
I've been worried about my showcase performance as it's getting closer and closer, and I'm not very confident about my dancing.
Is that all? Don't worry! Don't worry!
When it comes to dancing, as long as you can feel your passion, mistakes only exist...
When it comes to dancing, as long as you feel your passion, mistakes don't even exist!
Yeah, true! But I'm still a bit worried.
Well, in that case, how about this? Come to my jazz club. If we practice together, I'm sure you'll have more of a spring in your step!
Wait, right now? Well, that's really nice of you, Zaa senpai, but you know...
Okay, follow me, Liz.
Oh yeah, and dance...
Let's move and groove! Wait, what do you mean by move and groove?!
GIRI GIRIで愛しあいましょう
Let's love each other to the limit,
嘘も燃え尽くして 夢にして
burn up the lies and make it a dream.
冗談じゃない もっと踊りたい
No joke, I want to dance more,
もう我慢できない
I can't hold back anymore!
愛を 愛を 愛を 打ち明けてくれ
Give me your love, love, love, and confess it!
限界だ！ダー！
I'm at my limit! Da-da-da-da!
GIRA GIRAな 夢を 見せてよ
Show me a dazzling dream,
ぜんぶ ばらまいて 星にして
scatter it all and make them stars.
あぶないね その笑顔
Dangerous, that smile of yours,
こころ 乱されて 欲しくなる
it messes with my heart and I want more.
優等生 なんて 嘘でしょう
Being a model student must be a lie,
はぐらかして じれったい
you play dumb and it's so frustrating.
どうにかに なりそう
I feel like I'm losing my mind,
くちづける ほどに 足りなくな
the more we kiss, the less it feels enough.
抱き寄せたら 意外なほど
When I pull you close, surprisingly,
寂しい目で 見つめるから
you look at me with lonely eyes.
限界だ！ダー！
I'm at my limit! Da-da-da-da!
GIRA GIRAな 夢を 見せてよ
Show me a dazzling dream,
ぜんぶ ばらまいて 星にして
scatter it all and make them stars.
純情 じゃ ない ところも 知りたい
I want to know your uninnocent sides too.
もう我慢できない
I can't hold back anymore!
愛を 愛を 愛を 打ち明けてくれ
Give me your love, love, love, and confess it!
ドラマ なんて 飽きたでしょう
Aren't you tired of dramas?
ふたり だけの 最終回 描かなきゃ
We've got to draw our own finale.
運命 なんて じゃれ合って
Dallying with destiny,
演じきれば いいじゃない
isn't it fine if we just play our roles?
不器用な 言葉で また 覚悟を 試してくるのに
Even though you test my resolve again with clumsy words,
「ひとりきりに させないでよ」と 悲しい目で 笑うから
smiling with sad eyes as you say, "Don't leave me alone."
ズルいよな！ナ！ナ！ナ！
You're so unfair! Na-na-na-na!
GIRI GIRIな 恋人たちは
Lovers living on the edge
切ない この夜 も 満たすね
satisfy even this painful night.
理性 じゃ ない もっと 奥の 方
Not with reason, but from deep within,
ふるえて ヤバくなる
shivering and going crazy.
愛を 愛を 愛を 露わにしてくれ
Expose your love, love, love to me.
泣かないで それ以上
Don't cry any more than that,
こころ 撃ち抜かないで
don't shoot straight through my heart.
潤わせた 瞳 に もう 狂わされてしまう
Driven mad already by those moistened eyes.
完璧な 敗北さ もう離れ なんてしない
A total defeat, I won't let go anymore—
この指を この愛を
this finger, this love!
GIRI GIRIで 信じて欲しい
I want you to believe in us on the edge,
ふたり なら 真実になれる
if it's the two of us, we can become truth.
告白は 最後の 誓いさ もう抱きしめ たいよ
The confession is our final vow, I want to hold you tight.
GIRI GIRI で 愛し合いましょう
Let's love each other on the edge!
嘘 も 燃え尽き て 夢 に し て
Burn through the lies and turn them into dreams!
冗談じゃない もっと踊りたい
No joke, I want to dance more.
もう我慢できない 愛を愛を愛を打ち明けてくれ
I can't hold back anymore, confess your love to me!
あぶない ね その 笑顔
That smile is so dangerous.
こころ 乱さ れ て 欲しく なる
It makes my heart go wild.
シャララララ...
Sha-la-la-la-la...
はあ
Phew...
So, how was it?
Once you get into it, it's a good feeling, right?
Dance like nobody's watching, have fun!
Yes, somehow I really gained confidence. Thank you, Zeta-senpai.
Oh, Liz, you always tell others "mistakes help them grow" and believing in themselves...
You really need to start taking your own advice. Listen to your own heart's flame. Let that be your strength.
Yeah, you're right. Sometimes I forget, but thank you for reminding me. Guess I'm only human.
Here, let me help you take that off.
Hey, but it looks so dapper though, in it?
Hey, but it looks so dapper though, doesn't it?
Looks are cool!
Oh, shoot!
With you Liz, I'm sure your debut will be wonderful. I'm looking forward to it.
But with you, Liz, I'm sure your debut will be wonderful. I'm looking forward to it.
As you say, "Believe in me."
Who believes in thee? Huzzah!
Well, the preparations for the showcase seem to be going smoothly.
So much has happened since we infiltrated Holo. Songs, performances, troubles, challenges, and kind words, too.
All of them are irreplaceable memories I'll cherish forever.
I want to do my best for my family, my friends, my kingdom, and of course, my talented girlies, Justice!
Onwards and upwards!
Flame off!
Whew, it's been such a busy day.
Maybe I should rest for a bit...
Get a little, a little nap wouldn't hurt anybody. I mean... manages as I should nap anyways, so whatever.
Take a little... a little nap wouldn't hurt anybody. I mean... manages as I should nap anyways, so whatever.
顔を合わせれば喧嘩してばかり
Whenever we saw each other all we did was fight.
それもいい思い出だった
But those were also wonderful memories.
きみが教えてくれたんだ もう怖くない
You taught me so much, I'm not scared anymore.
どんな不自由でも 幸せは掴める だから
No matter how difficult, I can grab hold of happiness.
ひとりでもゆくよ 例え辛くても
I'll go by myself, even if it looks painful.
きみと見た夢は 必ず持ってくよ
I'll always carry on the dream I had with you.
ひとりでもゆくよ 死にたくなっても
I'll go by myself, even if I want to die,
声が聞こえるよ 死んではいけないと
I can hear your voice, I mustn't die.
例え辛くても 寂しさに泣いてても
Even if it looks painful, even if I'm crying in sadness,
他の誰でもない
No one else
でも目覚めた朝 きみはいないんだね
When I woke up, you weren't there.
ずっと遊べてる そんな気がしてた
I felt that we could play forever.
気がしていただけ わかっていた
I knew that's just what I believed.
生まれてきたことも もう後悔はしない
I don't regret being born any longer.
祭りの後みたい 寂しいけどそろそろ行こう
Like after a festival, sad but let's move on.
どこまでもゆくよ ここで知ったこと
I'll go anywhere, knowing what I learned.
幸せという夢を 叶えてみせるよ
I'll show you I can grant your happiness.
きみと離れても どんなに遠くなっても
Even if separated, no matter how far,
新しい朝に あたしは生きるよ
I'll live on in the new morning.
ひとりでもゆくよ
I'll go by myself,
死にたくなっても 声が聞こえるよ 死んではいけないと
even if I want to die, I hear your voice.
たとえ辛くても 寂しさに泣いていても
Even if painful, even if crying in sadness,
心の奥には 温もりを感じるよ
deep in my heart I feel your warmth.
巡って流れて 時は移りゆいた
Time changed as it ebbed and flowed.
もう何があったか 思い出せないけど
I can't remember what happened anymore,
目を閉じれば 誰かの笑い声が
if I close my eyes, someone's laughter...
なぜかそれが今 一番の宝物
Somehow that's now my most precious treasure.
ひとりでもゆくよ
I'll go by myself...
どこまでもゆくよ
I'll go anywhere...
唔...
Mmh...
はぁ～
Hah...
Oh, that dream...
What a beautiful, touching song.
You know what? I should probably add that to my showcase.
My showcase!
Oh no!
Flame on!
I'm gonna be late for my showcase, what the fudge?
My showcase! My showcase! My showcase!
Opening door!
Let's go! Come on!
My Bloodflame Kingdom! How is the performance thus far?
Rosarians!
Let me know what you all think using the hashtag #ERB3D.
What have you loved most thus far? Is it this beautiful theater?
The Queen Mother Theater, named after me, mum!
Hi mum! Hehe. Hello!
Was it Ollie's appearance? Flare on?
And Ollie's voiceovers? Kobo, Kaela, or Mumei sung with Armis?
Gigi, Gura with Zeta? Oh gosh, it would make me super-duper happy hearing your thoughts.
And by the way, I can see you all right now! Oh my gosh, I see you guys!
I've seen you at the corner of my eye with a magical invisible box
made by the Rosarian invisible wizards!
So I can see you all right now! Oh my gosh!
This is crazy.
What do you what do you think about my 3D appearance, huh? Huh?
Uh, let me know in chat right now what poses you would like to see.
Yeah, yeah, let me know. While you're doing that, I'm gonna go get Thorn.
Yeah! It's the one, the only
Thorn! Hello, I'm Thorn!
Let's do a quick pose with Thorn, shall we?
Hazaah! Hazaah!
All right, let's see what you guys have put.
Um... a cat pose?
All right, sure. Let me just put Thorn over here.
Let's take the jacket off for this one. Flame off!
Okay, I need to become Raora. Nyan, nyan, nyan.
Nyan, nyan, nyan, nyan, nyan.
T-pose?
Okay! That one's easy.
Yes, I shall assert my dominance on you all.
Oh, you know what I want to do?
I want to headpat you all. Come here, I headpat.
Headpat, headpat, and hug. Hug! We must do this, we must hug! Hug, hug!
Ah, one more! We got it, we got it.
What else have you all put?
Victory pose, like this?
Ha!
Yes, I am victorious! For I am the queen of the Bloodflame Kingdom!
Yeah.
I love you all very much, team! So happy you're all here.
Oh gosh...
Absolute cinema, yes.
Oh, a 12? Okay, we shall do a 12.
All right.
12.
Woah!
Whoa!
Is that okay? A 12?
Jazz hands!
Spin-! Spinna! Do we na...
Oh gosh. A curtsey? Oh, that's a good one.
Like this... I curtsey...
And a bow!
Hehe cute. Hey, you mean- you mean- you mean powerful, right?
Heh, cute. Hey, you mean—you mean—you mean powerful, right?
Powerful! Yes, yes, yes, powerful!
Rawr!
I know you guys also like my shocked face, so let me just think of something real shocking.
The frick!
What the frick!
What the frick! Time is nearly up for poses.
Oh, I guess it's time for the next song.
Would you like to hear another song? Yes, sure you do!
All right, just wait one moment. I need some, uh, some bits and bobs for this one.
All right. Some bits and the bobs and the bobs and the bits...
Here we go. Here's the bits and the bobs. I have a stand.
It's my mic! Look at that!
And I have a guitar!
Ha! I'm so kawaii!
All right. Uh, let's go with a, with a cute, I mean, a powerful song next.
Please listen to "Watashi no Koi wa Hotchkiss".
The next song is "My Love is a Stapler".
Let's go!
なんでなんだろ 気になる夜 キミへの
Why, what is it? On a night when you're on my mind
この想い 便箋にね 書いてみるよ
I'll try writing down my thoughts for you on some stationery
もしかして 気まぐれかもしれない
Perhaps it just might be a whim
それなのに 枚数だけ 増えていくよ
Yet even so, only the sheets increase in number
好きの 確率 わりだす 計算 式 あればいいのに
If only there was a formula for calculating the probability of love
キラキラ ひかる 願い事 も
Sparkling and shining wishes
グチャグチャへたる 悩み事 も
and messy and tiresome worries -
そーだ ホッチキス で とじ ちゃおー
that's right, I'll staple them together with a stapler
はじまり だけ は 軽い ノリ で
Only the beginning felt light
しらない うちに あつく なって
while I wasn't aware, it got thick
もう 針 が なんだか 通ら ない
and somehow the staple won't go through anymore
ララ ☆ また明日
La la ☆ see you tomorrow
どうしよう かな 読み返す の はずかしい
What shall I do? Rereading it is embarrassing
あれこれ と 便箋にね 書いた くせ に
despite that I wrote this and that on the stationery
気持ち ごと ゴミ箱 行き じゃ なんだか
if all of my feelings go to waste
この 胸 が せつない から 持っていこう かな
then somehow my chest will ache, so shall I keep them?
今の 気持ち を あらわす 辞書 に も ない 言葉 さがす よ
For expressing my current feelings I'll search for words that aren't even in dictionaries
ワクワクしちゃう 計画 とか
Whether it's a plan that makes me excited
グダグダすぎる 展開 とか
or a development that drags on too much
全部 ホッチキス で とじ ちゃおー
I'll staple them all together with a stapler
今日の できごと 想い出して
Recalling today's events
いつも 心 が キュン となって
my heart always feels a squeeze
もう 針 がない から 買わなきゃ
and since I no longer have staples, I've got to go buy some
わたしの恋はホッチキス
My love is a stapler,
ことば さがすよ
searching for words.
ワクワクしちゃう計画とか
Exciting plans
ぐちゃぐちゃすっきり展開とか
and messy yet satisfying developments,
全部ホッチキスでとじちゃおう
let's seal them all with a stapler,
とじちゃおー
let's seal them!
今日の出来事思い出して
Remembering today's events,
いつも心がキュンとなって
my heart always goes kyun,
もう針がないから
since I'm out of staples,
買わなくちゃ
I have to buy some!
ララ また明日
La la, see you tomorrow.
キラキラひかる願い事も
Shining wishes
グチャグチャへたる悩み事も
and messy, sagging worries,
そうだ ホッチキスでとじちゃおう
yes, let's seal them with a stapler,
とじちゃおー
let's seal them!
始まりだけは軽いノリで
Only the beginning had a light mood,
しらないうちに あつくなって
before I knew it, it got heated,
もう針がないんだから
the needles won't go through
とらない
anymore...
ララ また明日
La la, see you tomorrow.
And that was "My Love Is a Stapler."
How was it? Did you like my guitar playing?
I, well, you guys know this, but...
I'm actually a professional air guitarist!
I know, I know!
Surprise, shocker, professional air guitarist here. Look out!
Anywho, now it's time for an announcement!
Everyone, let's call for our favorite four-legged friend, Bobby!
3, 2, 1, Bobby!
Come here, Bobby, you're such a good boy!
Yes, you're a good boy!
Yeah, show yourself to the camera, do a little twirl or something, yeah.
Oh, you're so cute! Wait a minute, what the freak, Bobby!
Come here, come here, come here. Oh, big head!
Ah, good boy...
He's such a little, little cheeky guy.
Little cheeky guy! Oh golly.
Well, as you can see on Bobby's head, the announcement is... merchandise!
Oh my goodness, we have this!
Paper knife and acrylic stand.
A paper knife, letter opener, inspired by my sword, Thorn.
A set product that includes an acrylic stand where you can plop your mini thorn into.
It looks real cool on your desk and you'll get all the maidens.
I should know, a lot of them visited my, my dressing room to see the, the prototype.
And that's no lie, it's pretty awesome.
And also, the sales dates will be after the Justice collaboration stream.
So once that's all done and dusted, it'll be out there on the shop.
And that concludes the merchandise. Thank you, Bobby!
Everybody thank Bobby!
Thank you, Bobby! Thank you so much! You're such a good boy!
All right, back to the Duke and the Queen mother you go.
Oh gosh, I honestly can't believe it, time has flown.
And it's already time for our last, final seventh song, Seven!
This has been quite the journey and a half, so before I end, I just want to thank everyone,
the cast, our wonderful guests, the crew, managers, the director.
Thank you so much, thank you for your hard work, thank you, thank you so much.
And of course, my friends, my family, my beautiful kingdom.
Thanks for supporting me so much, I wouldn't be standing here right now.
Not only do I get to fight for justice, but with my wonderful girlies...
and Celia, but I also get to do
what I love. So thank you so much.
I get to give the gift of smiles and strength through the art of performance and singing.
I hope I can do this forever
and we can keep spreading smiles throughout the realms together, making me so happy.
Anyway, before the allergies hit me too much, let me just move my stand.
Allergies, guys, the allergies. I can't stand this stand! It must get out of the way.
Don't mind me.
All right, wait a minute. Before I do my last tune, we got to bring back my beautiful backing dancers, right?
Come on, flame on!
And they're back.
Are you ready? Are you ready?
Yes, yes, yes.
And now, for our final song, please listen to Hero Too!
Hands up! I want to be an idol and a hero for all of you too! Let's go!
What am I to be?
What is my calling?
I gave up giving up, I'm ready to go
The future's left unseen
It all depends on me
Put it on the line to follow my dream, yeah
Tried all my life
I've tried to find
Something that makes me hold on and never let go
Oh!
Hero too, I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe
So wait and see
Who do you think of me?
Who do you think I'll be?
I could not care less, I don't wanna know
Am I doing right?
Am I satisfied?
I wanna live my life like it's meant to be, yeah
Tried all my life,
I've tried to find
Something that makes me hold on and never let go
Oh!
Hero too, I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe, so wait and see
People will judge for no reason at all
Yeah, they might try to say your dream's dumb, don't listen
They may look down on me and count me out
I'm going my own way
I'm a hero, I've got music
Hero too, I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe
Yeah, I'll be!
Hero too, I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too, strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe, so wait and see
I have met so many heroes in my life who gave me the strength and courage to survive
Gave me the power to smile everyday
Now it's my turn to be the one to make you smile
What am I to be?
What is my calling?
I gave up giving up, I'm ready to go
The future's left unseen
It all depends on me
Put it on the line to follow my dream, yeah
Tried all my life
I've tried to find
Something that makes me hold on and never let go
Oh
Hero too
I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too
Strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe
So wait and see
What do they think of me?
Who do they think I'll be?
I could not care less, I don't wanna know
Am I doing right?
Am I satisfied?
I wanna live my life like it's meant to be, yeah
Tried all my life
I've tried to find
Something that makes me hold on and never let go
Oh
Hero too
I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too
Strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe
So wait and see
People will judge for no reason at all
Yeah, they might try to say your dream's dumb, don't listen
They may look down on me and count me out
I'm going my own way
I'm a hero, I've got music
Hero too
I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too
Strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe
Yeah, I'll be
Hero too
I am a hero too
My heart is set and I won't back down
Hero too
Strength doesn't make a hero
True heroes stand up for what they believe
So wait and see
I have met so many heroes in my life
Gave me the strength and courage to survive
Gave me the power to smile everyday
Now it's my turn to be the one to make you smile
Dear Rosarians, my beautiful sparks of joy...
Thank you for making my wishes come true! BIG HUGS, my Bloodflame Kingdom - Liz
Thank you for making my wishes come true! Big hugs, my Bloodflame Kingdom — Liz